# Andrei Marin

Quezon City, National Capital Region, Philippines

andreimarin1622@gmail.com

+639999951973

linkedin.com/in/andrei-marin-6a338620a

## Summary

Currently a consistent Dean's Lister Fourth-Year BS Information Systems Undergraduate from De La Salle University. I have basic to advanced knowledge of Full-Stack Web Development, Mobile Application Development, Database Management, Systems Development, and Object-Oriented Programming. I am also experienced in leading projects as well as working with a team.

### **Experience**



### **M** Development Lead

User Experience Society -DLSU Oct 2023 - Present (2 months)

### **Frontend Developer Intern**

**Baytech BPO Corporation** Sep 2023 - Dec 2023 (4 months)



De La Salle University

## Vice President - Human Resource Development

La Salle Computer Society Jan 2023 - Sep 2023 (9 months)

## Time Director for Student Services - DLSU CSG

University Student Government, De La Salle University Oct 2021 - Present (2 years 2 months)

## Executive for Web Design and Development, Office of the Secretary

University Student Government, De La Salle University Nov 2021 - Aug 2022 (10 months)

#### Associate Vice President for Socio Civic

La Salle Computer Society Oct 2021 - Aug 2022 (11 months)

## Deputy College General for College of Computer Studies

### Santugon sa Tawag ng Panahon

Feb 2021 - May 2022 (1 year 4 months)

## CATCH 2T24 BS INSYS Program Representative

University Student Government, De La Salle University Oct 2021 - Mar 2022 (6 months)

## Executive for Communications and Publicity - DLSU CSG

University Student Government, De La Salle University Apr 2021 - Sep 2021 (6 months)

### **Education**



Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Systems 2020 - 2024

### **Licenses & Certifications**

Shopee Code League 2022 - Participant - Shopee

### **Skills**

Leadership • Full-Stack Development • React.js • Vue.js • Firebase • Mobile Application Development • PHP • Flutter • Kotlin • Information Systems